hummingbirdhigh.com 2019-12-21

# PRIVACY | hummingbird high || a desserts and baking blog

This privacy policy sets out how Hummingbird High uses and protects any information that you give while using www.hummingbirdhigh.com.

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Hummingbird High may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. We encourage you to check this page from time to time to stay informed about how we are protecting the information that we collect. This policy is effective from May 25, 2018.

**Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personal identification information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, subscribe to receive updates, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. You may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. You can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal Identification Information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about you whenever you interact with our site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How We Use Cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets us know when you visit a particular page. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your’ needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your’ preferences.

A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data that you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify the browser setting to decline cookies.

**Cookies Opt-Out**

You can also opt out of cookies using the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at this page:  
http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/

Finally, you can choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings.

**What We Do with the Information We Gather**

Hummingbird High may use the collected information in the following ways:

  * _Website Improvement._  We strive to improve the website based on the information and feedback that we get from you.
  * _Promotions/Contests_. The information we collect may be used in connection with any promotions, contests, or surveys on this site.
  * _E-mails_. We may use your e-mail address to respond to any questions or inquiries.
  * _Opt-In Mailing List._  If you opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive periodic e-mails that contain updates, news, or other related products from this website. You have the option to unsubscribe from receiving future e-mails by following the instructions in the footer of the e-mail.

**Advertising**

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests that you have shown by browsing on this and other sites; to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before; to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, operating system, web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites. Such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Sharing Your Personal Information**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
